<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Portfolio on Behrooz Shahri</title><link>https://behroozshahri.com/work/</link><description>Recent content in Portfolio on Behrooz Shahri</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://behroozshahri.com/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Active Sushi Group</title><link>https://behroozshahri.com/work/active-sushi-group/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://behroozshahri.com/work/active-sushi-group/</guid><description>I joined this restaurant group of four branches in Cape Town to focus on boosting delivery sales and improving operational efficiency. My role involved restructuring the menu, introducing new staff training guidelines, and leading the transition from traditional practices to a modern, delivery-focused approach.
Despite the challenge of implementing significant changes while the restaurants continued operating in their old style, we successfully doubled delivery sales. In addition, we maintained a 4.</description></item><item><title>CERANA BRANDING CO.</title><link>https://behroozshahri.com/work/cerana/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://behroozshahri.com/work/cerana/</guid><description>I founded this company and built a team of designers and marketing specialists to provide branding and marketing services for B2B clients. Over two years, we helped various companies strengthen their brand presence and marketing strategies.
Eventually, I closed the company to focus on a new startup I launched within this venture, evolving the brand from Cerana into Seranaz, which later became a successful online printing service.</description></item><item><title>Chain of Legends</title><link>https://behroozshahri.com/work/chain-of-legends/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://behroozshahri.com/work/chain-of-legends/</guid><description>I joined the team for a 3-month project to lead and achieve specific growth goals for this crypto-based game. My role was to design and implement new workflow processes focused on attracting new players and increasing the value of the in-game token.
Through coordinated strategies and execution, we successfully gained over 40,000 new players, and the token price rose by more than 30% during the project period.</description></item><item><title>Dastur Press</title><link>https://behroozshahri.com/work/dasturpress/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://behroozshahri.com/work/dasturpress/</guid><description>I began my career at this book publishing company while still a university student, working as a graphic designer. My main responsibility was creating book covers, which gave me early experience in blending creativity with client expectations.
This role was my first professional step into the creative industry and helped shape my design and visual communication skills.</description></item><item><title>Greentech Accelerator</title><link>https://behroozshahri.com/work/greentech/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://behroozshahri.com/work/greentech/</guid><description>As one of the pioneers of the startup community in my city, I joined this accelerator to help early-stage teams transform their ideas into viable business models. I guided startups in defining roadmaps from concept to growth, connecting them with investors, and refining their strategies.
In parallel, I organized events and collaborated with the marketing team to attract talented founders and mentors, helping strengthen the local startup ecosystem.</description></item><item><title>GREENWEB IT SERVICES</title><link>https://behroozshahri.com/work/greenweb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://behroozshahri.com/work/greenweb/</guid><description>Right after earning my bachelor’s degree in IT, I joined GreenWeb and began managing their social media presence, with a special focus on Instagram at a time when it was still a new and emerging platform. I worked across multiple brands, developing strategies to grow audiences and attract customers.
Over time, we expanded our services to bring in external clients for digital marketing solutions. In addition, I organized events and exhibitions that boosted the company’s visibility.</description></item><item><title>Hungarian Games L.L.C</title><link>https://behroozshahri.com/work/hungarian-games/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://behroozshahri.com/work/hungarian-games/</guid><description>I led customer experience, marketing, and event initiatives for this cooperative gaming company, managing day-to-day customer service operations and organizing brand events to strengthen engagement and visibility. I directed the marketing team, using data-driven insights from Google Analytics to optimize campaigns and improve overall customer satisfaction. This role allowed me to combine strategy, analytics, and hands-on customer interaction to enhance the brand’s reputation and growth.</description></item><item><title>SERANAZ ONLINE PRINTING SERVICE</title><link>https://behroozshahri.com/work/seranaz/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://behroozshahri.com/work/seranaz/</guid><description>Built this startup from the ground up with zero initial investment. The service allowed customers to send family photos online, which we then printed on high-quality materials and delivered to them. The concept addressed the growing desire for physical keepsakes, particularly albums for children.
Over nearly seven years, I grew the business to serve over 60,000 customers. Managing sensitive personal data was a key responsibility, and upon closing the business to relocate to Dubai, all customer data was securely deleted.</description></item></channel></rss>